Guide to the John B. Duncan papers, 1932-1989 MS2055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1960-1968; MS2055 Series 1; 4.5 Linear feet
  - Photograph, Duncan and Boy Scout, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Duncan with unknown man, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Duncan Receiving Items from Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife at party, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at outdoor event, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Duncan at dinner at Marriott Motor Hotel, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Secretary at desk, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Continuous Monitoring Station, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Duncan Giving DC and US Flags to men, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Duncan with three unidentified men, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Merit to David Sawyer, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Giving Key to City to Unidentified Men, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner at unknown press conference, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Duncan with unknown people, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Arrival of President of Sudan at airport, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at unknown event, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Duncan with retiring board members, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at The Mayflower, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Welcoming NIAA Eastern USA Conference to DC, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Retiring from Urban Renewal, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Duncan receives certificate, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group and Rosa Parks, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Two Men Playing Tennis, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Giving Key to Military, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan Shaking Hands with JFK, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Duncan Shaking Hands with JFK, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, At Meeting with Projector, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two men and two women, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Duncan in tuxedo with two men, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two unknown men, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Santa and woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two unknown men, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group of men, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Duncan Taking Oath, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Duncan at The Willard, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Duncan greeting unidentified man, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Duncan giving something to unidentified woman, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Duncan at The Mayflower, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Duncan Giving Certificate, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Greetings, U.F.W. Ladies' Auxiliary, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, Duncan with people, bronze bust in background, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Duncan with people receiving oath, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Duncan Receiving Pen from LBJ, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Autographed, Hubert Humphrey, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Autographed, LBJ and Duncan, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, 10th Anniversary, Museum of African Art, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Duncan, JFK and Boy, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Duncan at White House with JFK, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Speeches, 1953-1978; MS2055 Series 2; 3.5 Linear feet
  This series contains speeches delivered by Duncan from 1953-78. Duncan's addresses and statements document his professional career from his appointments as recorder of deeds through his retirement. Note cards used by Duncan to deliver the speeches are included with many of the texts.
  - Speech, 1953 March 22 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1954 June 02 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1954 December 12 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1955 May 16 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Speech, Circa 1959 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1960 January 25 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1961 February 20 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1961 March 07 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1961 April 09 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1961 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1961 June 28 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1961 July 09 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1961 July 24 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1961 August 10 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1961 August 13 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1961 August 17 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1961 August 30 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1961 September 02 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1961 October 09 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1961 October 17 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1961 October 20 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Empty File, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1961 October 24 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1961 October 24 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1961 November 07 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1961 November 20 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1961 November 21 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1961 November 30 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1961 November 30 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1961 December 05 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Speech, 1961 December 11 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Speech, 1961 December 11 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Speech, 1962 January 01 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1962 January 15 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1962 January 15 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1962 January 22 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1962 January 23 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1962 January 24 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1962 January 28 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1962 February 03 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1962 February 10 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1962 February 11 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1962 February 15 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1962 February 16 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1962 February 18 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1962 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1962 February 25 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1962 February 26 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1962 February 27 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1962 March 05 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1962 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1962 April 04 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1962 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Speech, 1962 April 26 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1962 May 04 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1962 May 09 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1962 May 09 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1962 May 10 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1962 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1962 May 23 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1962 June 06 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1962 June 12 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Speech, 1962 June 13 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Speech, 1962 June 14 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Speech, 1962 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Speech, 1962 June 25 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Speech, 1962 July 04 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1962 July 18 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1962 July 20 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1962 July 30 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1962 July 31 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1962 September 06 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1962 October 01 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1962 October 04 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1962 October 09 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1962 October 19 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1962 October 21 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1962 October 26 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1962 November 14 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1962 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1962 November 27 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1962 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1963 January 17 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1963 January 27 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1963 January 30 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1963 February 18 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1963 February 25 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Speech, 1963 February 27 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1963 March 26 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1963 April 02 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1963 April 11 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1963 April 19 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1963 April 22 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1963 April 30 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1963 May 08 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1963 June 02 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Speech, 1963 June 13 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Speech, 1963 June 17 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Speech, 1963 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Speech, 1963 July 13 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Speech, 1963 July 17 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Speech, 1963 August 07 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1963 August 26 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1963 September 10 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1963 September 18 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1963 October 07 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1963 October 08 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1963 October 16 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1963 November 20 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1963 November 20 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1963 December 06 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1963 December 31 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1964 January 23 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1964 February 08 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1964 March 07 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1964 April 04 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1964 April 07 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1964 April 13 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1964 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1964 April 19 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1964 April 22 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1964 April 29 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Speech, 1964 May 08 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1964 May 08 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1964 May 22 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1964 June 03 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1964 June 10 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1964 June 29 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1964 June 30 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1964 July 04 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1964 August 10 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Speech, 1964 September 09-11 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Speech, 1964 September 09 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Speech, 1964 September 15 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Speech, 1964 September 17 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Speech, 1964 September 26 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Speech, 1964 September 26 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Speech, 1964 September 28 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Speech, 1964 October 10 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1964 October 14 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1964 October 23 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1964 October 29 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1964 November 03 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1965 January 22 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1965 February 02 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1965 April 27 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1965 May 04 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1965 May 08 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1965 May 13 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1965 May 17 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1965 May 24 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1965 June 02 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1965 June 17 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1965 June 25 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1965 June 30 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1965 July 01 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1965 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1965 September 14 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1965 September 21 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Speech, 1965 September 27 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1965 October 21 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1965 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1965 November 17 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1965 November 21 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1966 January 17 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1966 February 15 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1966 February 27 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1966 March 04 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Speech, 1966 March 09 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Speech, 1966 March 24 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Speech, 1966 April 04 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Speech, 1966 April 04 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Speech, 1966 April 24 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Speech, 1966 May 03 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1966 May 10 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1966 May 11 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1966 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1966 May 25 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1966 May 25 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1966 June 02 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1966 July 21 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1966 July 22 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1966 August 19 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1966 September 23 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1966 September 29 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1966 October 07 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1966 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1966 October 19 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1966 October 28 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1966 November 10 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1966 November 10 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1966 December 15 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Speech, 1967 January 12 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Speech, 1967 January 13 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Speech, 1967 January 19 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Speech, 1967 January 24 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Speech, 1967 February 14 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 1967 February 23 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Speech, 1967 March 03 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Speech, 1967 March 22 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Speech, 1967 March 23 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Speech, 1967 April 12 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Speech, 1967 May 02 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Speech, 1967 May 05 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Speech, 1967 May 18 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Speech, 1967 May 19 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Speech, 1967 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Speech, 1967 May 29 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Speech, 1967 June 05 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Speech, 1967 June 13 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Speech, 1967 June 19 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Speech, 1967 June 30 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Speech, 1967 July 12 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Speech, 1967 July 17 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Speech, 1968 June 11 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Speech, 1968 June 19 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Speech, 1972 September 07 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Speech, 1973 January 24 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Speech, 1974 January 27 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Speech, 1976 March 14 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Speech, 1978 January 27 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Speech, Program of Teaching Career Month [04/05/?], Year? April 05 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Speech, Rally of United Democrats for Johnson, Year? April 12 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Speech, LaFayette Square USO, Year? July 01 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Speech, International Printing Pressman's Union Convention, Year? September 28 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Speech, Notes on Samuel Peal, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Speech, 4th Congressional District Association, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Speech, Invocation, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Speech, Catholic University, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Speech, Outline of Speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Speech, Dedication of Washington, D.C. Continuous Air Monitoring Station, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Speech, Imhotep National Conference, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Speech, Twelfth Annual Meeting of the D.C. Public Health Association, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Speech, Ford Foundation Grant to UPO, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Speech, Louisville District Conference, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Speech, Statement, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Speech, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Speech, Youth Conference at Livingstone College, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Speech, Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Speech, Questions for Durham, North Carolina Conference, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Correspondence, 1960-1982; MS2055 Series 3; 1 Linear feet
  This series contains correspondence dated from 1960-82. This correspondence is from Duncan's tenure as recorder of deeds and DC Commissioner. Requests for speeches, letters regarding various social councils, thank you notes to and from Duncan, as well as character references may be reviewed.
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1961 March-May (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1961 July-December (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1962 January-February (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1962 March-May (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1962 June-August (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1962 September-December (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1963 January-March (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1963 April 06 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1963 July-September (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1963 October-December (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1964 January-May (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1964 June-December (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1965 January-April (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1965 May-December (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1966 January-December (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1967 January-December (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1968 January-March (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1968 April-August (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1968 September-December (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Greeting cards, Circa 1965; Series 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Honors and awards, 1961-1989; MS2055 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of certificates and programs for awards Duncan received to honor his support of various private organizations. These materials date from 1961-89.
  - Honors and Awards, Program, The Brotherhood Dinner, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Honors and Awards, Ticket, Big Brothers Testimonial Dinner, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Honorary Membership, G.U.O. of O., America, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Honors and Awards, Program, Sons and Daughters Day Foundation Luncheon, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Award, Member of the Celebrity Softball Team, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Honors and Awards, Livingstone College Memento to Gift In Auditorium, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Appreciation, DC Chapter of the American Red Cross, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Honors and Awards, Citation, Self-Determination for DC Coalition, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Honors and Awards, Commendation from Gerald Ford, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Honors and Awards, Resolution, Appreciation to Members of the D.C. Inaugural Committee, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Honors and Awards, Booklet, Golden Anniversary of DePriest Fifteen (1933 to 1983) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Appreciation, Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Appreciation, Democratic Presidential Trust, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Recognition, Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Honors and Awards, Recognition, Southern Poverty Law Center, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Honors and Awards, Resolution, Honorary Trustee of The George Washington University Board, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Award, W.A.L. Youth Affairs Committee, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Appreciation, Watergate at Landmark Condominium Unit Owners Assoc., 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Honors and Awards, GW Report school paper on Duncan receiving his honorary degree of Doctor of Public Service, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Honors and Awards, Certificate of Participation, The 2nd Annual Self-Esteem Program, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Honors and Awards, Business Leaders Rally, Red Feather Award, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Reference files, 1954-1989; MS2055 Series 5; 2 Linear feet
  This series contains biographies, invitations, programs, brochures papers, reports, speeches, travel authorizations, and directories. This material is dated from 1954-89. The subject files contain biographies for seven D.C. officials including James Elliott Coates, Norman Holly, and Philip Shandler. There are also files with information about the Washington D.C. government such as a constitution, chart of government offices, and papers on the Joint Committee on the National Capital and advisory panel to the President's special task force. Invitations and programs from a variety of events. Legalized gambling reports, mental health brochures, NAACP reports, the National Capital Downtown Committee papers, Negro solidarity reports, and the President's Council on Pennsylvania Avenue papers are included in the reference files. The largest section of this series is speeches delivered by other individuals and retained by Duncan for inspiration and reference. Other material contained in this series include U.S. House and Senate telephone directories, travel authorization papers, a USO survey, Washington Urban League material and information on the Work Release Plan and Youth Opportunity Campaign.
  - Reference Files, Biographies, DC Notables, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reference Files, Democratic Speech Kit for the Accomplishments of the Congress and the Executive Branch, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Reference Files, Department of Occupations & Professions, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Constitution of the "District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations, Incorporated", 1954 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Flow Chart of positions in the government, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, The Budget of the District of Columbia, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Booklet on the Government of DC, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Joint Committee on the National Capital, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Advisory Panel to President's Special Task Force, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Reference Files, DC Government, Timeline for the Transition from Three Commissioner Government to Appointed Commissioner/Council Government, Circa 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Reference Files, Editorial from WTOP radio station, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Reference Files, Employment, Report, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Reference Files, Employment Forms for two unrelated people, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Reference Files, Fire Prevention Code Booklet, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, Testimonial Banquet, A.M.E. Church, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, Inaugural Events, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, Dinner at the National Zoo and Regents' Dinner, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, National Geographic Society Dinner, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, DePriest Fifteen Annual Dinner, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Reference Files, Invitations and Programs, GWU Convocation in Honor of Fortieth President of US, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Reference Files, Legalized Gambling, Discussion for the District of Columbia, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Reference Files, Legalized Gambling, Appendix I of the Citizens' Gambling Study Commission Report, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Reference Files, Legalized Gambling, Appendix II of the Citizens' Gambling Study Commission Report, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Reference Files, Mental Health, Brochures, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)